Officially wrapped.
Cheers.
He's leaving?
I hope that you find
your own love and happiness
on your own moon.
I think getting to know everyone
is a very happy thing.
We'll meet again.
Goodbye.
We must meet again.
Bye-bye.
Time to go home and cook.
You did so well.
Let me give you a painting.
Okay.
Xiaowen is smiling so much
that he has dimples.
What are you doing?
I can't take it anymore.
You just ate a lot of...
So sudden.
Sorry.
We're like we've never
seen the world before.
Whether it works out or not,
I like you anyway.
What I like is you as a person.
There's a fragrance.
Yes.
Smell it.
So, if you leave the house,
what's the first thing you want to do?
Sleep.
Catch up on sleep.
What else?
I won't say it.
You tell me yours first.
Exchange WeChat.
I was just about to say that.
They don't have each other's
contact info right now.
I really...
Now, I really still will...
Sometimes,
like when I wake up,
I'll subconsciously want
to pull up WeChat.
Then I suddenly realize
I don't have WeChat.
Exchange WeChat and chat freely.
Do you mean group chat or...
Private chat.
That's great.
I think today's schedule
made me feel
much more relaxed than I expected.
On the way there today,
he was comforting me,
telling me not to be nervous.
Then after we arrived at his home,
he didn't even
force me to chat with his parents.
Let me show you around.
It was just very comfortable overall.
And also,
during the meal,
he took good care of me.
He kept putting food on my plate
and peeling shrimp for me.
And what made me feel safe was that,
I think,
his overall family atmosphere
was really harmonious.
And it didn't make me feel any pressure
or any discomfort
of meeting the elders
in such
a formal setting.
I would really look forward to this kind
of harmonious family,
and maybe
the scene of a loving mother
and filial children.
Yes.
Rest well tonight.
Uncle and auntie,
you should also rest early.
Okay, bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
See you tomorrow.
Okay, careful.
Get on first.
Bye-bye.
Put this in the back.
How do you feel?
What's so funny?
I'm very grateful to your parents.
I'm very envious of you.
I think I brought Liu home
mainly to let her experience
my family atmosphere.
It's a relatively loving,
a relatively relaxed family atmosphere.
Yeah, I just hope that
she doesn't have too many worries
in this aspect.
Let's do it again.
Aren't you tired?
Wait. Why
are there
two voices,
but I can only see one person's feet?
I'm dying laughing.
Alright.
Okay.
This one.
The last one is so funny.
I can't take it.
I think being with Xiaowen
is really fun.
Yeah.
He always looks for fun.
He's always looking for fun.
He's a very interesting guy.
Yeah.
Soon, everyone will be parting ways.
We're in the countdown.
Are you reluctant to part?
Definitely.
Who will you miss the most?
Do you even need to ask?
They're flirting, you know.
Save your "humph".
Boring.
One asks despite knowing the answer.
The other knows but won't say.
What?
Xiaowen really likes
being teased
by Xuan's teasing.
Yeah.
Do you think
if in real life,
we really encountered
each other,
would we actually try
to get to know each other?
What do you think?
If you met someone like me
in your life,
would you get to know them?
I think if,
let's say,
maybe I have a friend,
and you're a friend of my friend,
if we meet each other,
I think I'd probably add you on WeChat.
Then we might
occasionally hang out together,
or something.
That means no matter what,
I'll still like you.
But I think it's still hard for us
like this.
What?
We're not even in the same city.
That's true.
When this is over,
you'll go back to Beijing.
(Shanghai, Beijing)
I think that time you woke me up.
That is, some things
don't necessarily need an answer.
So you've changed your mind to this now?
Why are you sitting so far away?
Being a sister.
Do you have to make me say it?
What an episode!
I just love watching this kind of thing.
Actually, I like it too.
You know, the flirtation
reaches its peak.
And I like it when the girl
takes the initiative and says,
"Why are you sitting so far away?"
Yeah.
Come closer to me.
Is that what you mean?
The two of them sitting so sloppily.
It's very romantic.
We've been talking about playing tennis
since the beginning.
Tomorrow, we can finally play.
When did we say we'd play tennis?
We said it when we went to Sanya?
No way!
We said it before going to Sanya.
Really?
I wanted to invite you
to play tennis today,
so I really wanted to come out.
Yeah.
Xiaowen is just cute.
Xiaowen is really cute.
(The next day)
What time are we leaving?
Looking good!
We can head out now.
I'll just grab Zhou Youling's bag.
He said I can use whatever I want.
We're going to have
a fierce battle today.
Are we playing seriously?
We can do this.
Let's just play casually
for a while first.
Warm up on the small court first.
Yeah.
Okay.
(Warming up)
Are you really going to strip here?
(Don't look at what's improper)
You're being filmed again
while taking off your pants.
Just film.
(It's okay, all family here)
No outsiders here.
Let them film.
Just taking off pants.
Tiebreak.
Okay.
The loser
belongs to the winner.
The winner can arrange
and control the loser as they please,
okay?
Okay.
If you say so,
you'll definitely win, no matter what.
If you want to be dominated,
just deliberately say that.
(Jia Peixuan, Aspirant of Grand Slams)
Anyway, I was training
with a coach for a while back then.
(Xiao Wentao, Unknown in tennis parks)
I never learned.
The odd old men play very well.
You serve.
Nice shot.
Good.
(Out of bounds)
Come on!
Too late.
(Reward with a big slap)
Don't be like that. What are you doing?
Always...
Scary, right?
Always late.
Sorry, I'm so bad.
No.
Aren't you playing well?
Better than me and Zhou Youling.
Really?
That's right.
One point.
(Jia Peixuan 1:0 Xiao Wentao)
Why?
Just getting a feel for it.
(Good touch on the ball)
Start using feet now?
(Basic popping moves)
(Ball, are you coming back for dinner?)
Four to one.
(Jia Peixuan 4:1 Xiao Wentao)
I'm so fed up.
So bad it's embarrassing.
You're running me around.
One more.
Running me around.
Okay.
Side shuffle.
Are you playing tricks on me?
I didn't mean to.
It's my instinct.
Ugly expression.
Your expression is so ugly.
I saw an opening.
If I don't hit it, I feel uncomfortable.
It seems like Xuan is really
better than him.
Xuan is really amazing.
What are you doing?
Thanks for giving me a chance.
(The younger brother is showing off)
(Jia Peixuan 6:6 Xiao Wentao)
Six all.
Does it have to be this intense?
Tiebreak, six all.
Match point.
Who will dominate whom?
(Jia Peixuan 7:6 Xiao Wentao)
Very natural.
Listen to this sound,
and you can tell Xiaowen won.
Xiaowen won.
(The elder sister wins this game)
Xiaowen can be dominated now.
Congratulations Xiaowen on his victory.
I'm so tired.
How does it feel, my defeated opponent?
(The younger brother concedes)
Respect.
How does it feel?
I bow to you.
Sister, dominate me.
I haven't played this intensely
in a long time.
Mainly because it got too fast
at the end,
I just couldn't recover at the end.
I won.
I want to save up a big move.
Can't let him off easily.
I need to think about it carefully.
I really need to think this through.
What should we eat?
I'm treating.
You're treating?
A six-year age gap
is actually quite romantic.
What are you laughing at?
The environment is pretty nice.
Do you want a blanket
to cover your legs?
I'll go ask.
Thank you.
Do you want to cover yourself?
I don't need it. I'm not cold.
Do you think
that two people need to be good enough
before they can be together?
My logic is
that if it's a good relationship,
the two people must be
independent individuals.
It's definitely not
about what I need from you,
or what you can give me.
If we're together just for that,
it's not love.
Right.
If once
you can't give me
what I need,
and I become dissatisfied,
or can't accept it,
that's definitely
not a good relationship.
Right.
No matter how outstanding you are,
it's useless.
I think it's just two people
going through things together,
making mistakes together,
facing problems,
and solving them together.
I just think
that having no problems between a couple
is the biggest problem.
Really?
If there's no conflict,
then someone must be acting.
One side must be compromising.
Maybe they think
that this conflict
doesn't need to be resolved right now,
or I'm saving face,
or I don't want
to hurt the other person.
But it doesn't mean there's no conflict.
That's right.
That's very well said.
I think it might also
have something to do with my family.
That gave me this mindset.
Why?
Because
my parents separated
because of conflicts.
So I definitely think
that in a family, whether it's a couple
or a married couple,
there will inevitably be conflicts.
Did they ever fight in front of you?
Yes.
They argued, and they fought.
It was intense.
Childhood trauma.
That's really childhood trauma.
So do you think
after experiencing
your parents' situation,
it will affect your future marriage life
and love life?
Yes, it has a huge impact.
I subconsciously lack
a sense of security.
I will encounter
people I can't trust.
I need to stay away from them.
Even in a relationship,
I will doubt myself.
Do you doubt the other person
or yourself?
Both.
(People are very contradictory.)
(Those who say they don't care the most)
(are the ones
who face things cautiously.)
(It's all a form
of protective coloring.)
He wants me
to understand him better, I think.
So he talked
about his lack of security.
The source of his insecurity
is his parents' relationship.
I felt his sincerity
at that moment.
These things
are helpful.
That is, he can also understand me now.
The two of us maybe
will take a step closer in our hearts.
I gave up everything for him
and returned to Wuhan.
So after that happened,
for me,
yes, my whole world just collapsed.
My whole world really collapsed.
Then you'd fall into deep self-doubt,
like you chose this person yourself.
No one forced you
to take this step.
Am I really that bad at judging people?
Did I just fall in love
with such a person?
That self-doubt
was like you don't believe
anything anymore.
It's okay.
You've moved on.
Give a hug.
It's okay.
You've moved on.
A thousand words
can't compare to this one hug.
I think in the house,
Xuan is the most special one to me.
She almost showed me
her everything.
I think her experiences
have shaped her into who she is today.
To me,
she's really
shining.
I'm also willing to show her
more of myself.
(I think the two of them,
although very broken,)
(are very real.)
This is very rare.
Yeah.
Just now, Xiaowen
actually mentioned the same issue.
He said that some family reasons
also shaped his current view
on relationships.
He believes
that in the process
of two people getting along,
conflicts are inevitable.
I completely understand.
Having no problems
is actually a very big problem.
Right.
Because if there are no problems,
it's either the two people
interact too little.
Yeah.
This completely deviates
frim the foundation
of an intimate relationship.
Right.
The other problem is
when there are no problems,
it definitely means one side
is constantly compromising.
This is very scary.
Yeah.
One day, the compromising side
might explode.
Or one day, the one
who always benefits from the compromise
might feel there's no chemistry anymore.
Right.
It's just shallow.
So it breaks easily.
In sociology,
we divide marriage into two types.
(Homogamy, Heterogamy)
One is called homogamy.
The other is called heterogamy.
Homogamy is when
two very similar people are together.
Relatively speaking,
of course, there will be problems too.
But maybe the problems
are relatively fewer.
Heterogamy
is when two people
come from different family backgrounds,
different regions,
and have many inherent differences.
So when they are together,
you will find
that their differences and conflicts
are relatively more frequent.
My husband and I come
from completely different backgrounds.
So when we travel together,
my husband and I
will argue over the slightest thing.
Even experts argue, you know.
Even experts argue.
Of course, we argue.
Arguing is a good thing.
As everyone says,
arguing is a great way
to understand each other.
Yes.
The core
is not about how many problems we have,
but when we have differences,
whether both sides
can find a mutually acceptable way
to handle the conflict.
Yes.
It feels like
whether it's simmering on low heat,
or stir-frying on high heat,
as long as it tastes good, it's fine.
We just saw Zhou Youling
bring Liu home to meet his parents.
Is there any detail that you think
is particularly memorable now?
Would you girls think
the embrace move is...
It depends on the person.
Okay.
It's not really about the move.
So your girlfriend probably likes it.
Yeah.
When you like each other,
that embrace is very heartwarming.
Yeah.
I think it's just
Zhou Youling and Liu
meeting the parents
is probably their first time
leaving the house
and stepping into reality.
Yes.
At that moment,
their relationship must have heated up.
Because they took
another step forward together.
That really moved me when I watched it.
A guy meeting his in-laws
and a girl meeting her in-laws
are very different.
I'm telling you.
Only when the mother-in-law likes you
will she want to interrogate you.
If she's polite to you,
then you better watch out.
(Interrogation by the girl's parents)
You've been dating steadily these years.
(Sales pitch by the guy's parents)
So we're heading towards marriage.
What do you think?
He is quite family-oriented.
If there are good movies,
he'll take us to watch them.
He's the kind
of trendy warm-hearted guy.
First of all, you can see
the parents' attitudes are different.
Look at Zhou Youling's parents.
They said thing like,
(Nice, innocent, family-oriented)
"Our Zhou Youling is a good man.
Usually, he's blah blah.
He's very innocent.
He often comes home and so on."
Sales pitch.
Yes.
But the girl's parents were like,
"Don't be fooled by her now.
Her temper is huge.
(Deeply agreeing)
She is very..."
The first six months.
Only six months.
"Don't come complaining to me then."
Talk about shortcomings.
Yes.
All talk about shortcomings.
Guys' parents all talk about strengths.
I think, well...
We can see
that
Zhou Youling and Liu's personalities
might be somewhat different.
So everyone, do you think
that the family of origin
will have a big impact
in your future relationships?
Of course.
Definitely.
Because my parents also argue often.
Like bickering.
And I've seen a lot of it.
So I found
that I'm very afraid of arguing.
But sometimes, I easily
speak very hastily.
When emotions rise,
I can't control myself.
But my girlfriend
is the type who gives
a lot of emotional value.
So there's no chance to argue.
We also want to ask Ms. Shen.
How much impact
does the family of origin have?
It definitely has an impact.
But whether it's entirely determined
by the family of origin
is depends.
Because actually,
in the process of growing up,
factors like your school,
or your daily social interactions
will all affect it.
But actually,
I think what's very interesting
in this story
is that you will find
that the marital relationship itself
greatly affects the child's personality
and their emotional response patterns.
Yes.
I often tell
many parents
that pressuring your kids
to get married is actually useless.
The best way to encourage marriage
is to make
your own marriage life happier.
So that children
don't think it's so scary.
Appreciate your children a little more,
so that children don't feel
so bad about themselves.
Then the child can truly accept
intimate relationships.
Yes.
Parents are indeed
the best role models for children.
Yes.
(Today is a day)
(to pick up Ling Lizheng from work.)
(As I was about to arrive,
I was a bit nervous.)
(The night before)
Your novelty has worn off.
I don't think it's a bad thing.
Because I think
my fondness for you
is still increasing every day.
If the novelty fades,
and I still have a lot of fondness
for you,
that's what's more important to me.
I'm very happy
that you chose me.
And my choice remains the same.
And I hope
we continue to get to know each other.
Since things have progressed this far
with Ling Lizheng,
I really want to see and feel
whether he's the right person for me.
I haven't had this feeling
of nervousness for a long time.
The last time
was when I entered the Sanya house.
(It's windy today)
Besides nervousness, it was just cold.
So cold.
Ling Lizheng is especially handsome
in real life.
Did you expect this?
I didn't.
He was startled
in a very mechanical way.
Humorous.
Startled
in a very mechanical way.
I'm very happy.
When I was working today,
I was completely
in a state of almost drained battery.
Seeing you come, I feel
like there's a backup battery.
He's very happy.
Backup.
Power bank.
Yes.
Let's go eat together.
Okay.
I'll go get the menu.
Two, please. Thank you.
Why is it so cold inside here too?
Can you turn on the heater?
And a glass of hot water, please.
Wait, I'll turn on the heater
for you first.
Okay.
Thank you.
So thoughtful.
Yes.
What would you like to eat today?
Boneless chicken feet.
Let's have that.
I want to have something sour.
It's our first time dining
in a Western restaurant.
It's really nice.
One half for each of us here.
Our bond can never break.
Half.
Okay.
One of this.
No.
Enough.
It's good enough.
I'm very happy.
It feels so good to be picked up.
(Such a sweet talker.)
It feels like these past few days,
we haven't really seen each other much.
Yeah, I had work
right after I came back.
Even without work, I'd still fill
my daily schedule to the brim.
In the morning, I might go hiking.
Then I'll come back
and rest at eleven o'clock.
In the afternoon, a one-hour
personal training session,
meeting a friend for an hour,
then coming back home
for dinner in the evening.
After that, I'll work a little more.
Just reading something.
After maxing out the day's capacity,
I come back to sleep.
Then...
I find you're really very focused
on your career.
A workaholic.
I didn't notice it in Sanya.
After coming back,
I feel it more and more.
In Sanya?
In Sanya, I just handled
some work online.
When I first got to know you,
you were just so charming.
I've thrown everything
to the back of my mind.
Such a sweet talker.
The life I want is just
a simple one.
Dating after work, going home,
steady happiness.
Are you happy?
I am happy.
This is the life I want.
Well,
the life I want is...
Bro, I'm very embarrassed
to say it with you here.
(A lifetime of happiness together)
Okay, sorry.
Okay, no problem.
You're being too polite.
Is it my fault?
He wants to say something cheesy.
The life I want is
having both active
and passive income every day.
(They've gone far, right? No one's eavesdropping?)
After I'm done with work,
I have a wife, kids, and a warm bed.
It's hard to say such cheesy words.
Going back home, I'd be very happy.
Eating and sleeping together enjoybly.
(Of course, I really hope)
(to have such a life.)
Coming here, I certainly want
to find someone
I like.
Now I've probably found
such a person.
I definitely hope
that our goals can be aligned.
For our future development,
I think I have expectations.
What a rare scene.
Yeah.
This family atmosphere
is what Hui wants.
What's wrong?
It's very good.
Oh, no.
What's wrong?
You're in trouble.
You've fallen in love.
Let's go back.
Let's go.
It's the leather jacket again today.
Come on, let me button it.
Okay.
Let's go.
Are you tired?
Does your stomach hurt?
Can drinking water help?
(Drink more hot water)
It helps.
It doesn't help?
Just drink some now.
Not now.
Is the wind blowing on you bad?
Let's close it.
It's cold.
Holding hands is the most effective
at a time like this.
Let me test if it's too hot.
It shouldn't be hot.
It's not hot?
I just tested the temperature
with my hand, it's just fine.
It's just right.
Just right?
Why don't you lie down for a while?
It's the one on the left back
that can be adjusted.
Bottom left, yes.
Where?
It can adjust the back, right?
It can't be adjusted.
Forget it.
Let me do it.
What if it can be adjusted?
Why did the massage turn on?
How can you adjust it?
Okay, done.
It's a bit more comfortable like this.
You can lie down.
Is it okay?
Are you feeling a bit more comfortable?
You still came out today
even though you're on your period.
How should I put it?
I wanted to see you.
But today, I'm really...
Your body is too weak for it.
I understand now.
Thank you for today.
Well, I'm very happy to see you.
Oh, no.
(Heart gesture)
It should be like this.
Have a good rest.
Well,
nap for a while.
There are marks on your face.
Bye-bye.
If I go out like this
holding a bottle of milk, would I be...
(There's an opening ceremony today.)
(It is)
(a very important moment)
(in my entrepreneurial establishment.)
(The night before last)
If the opening is the day after tomorrow,
will you invite your friends?
Really?
Last time, I went
to pick her up from work
and I saw her work environment.
Today, I'm bringing her here
to witness my work state.
It's so beautiful.
It's good, right?
It's nice.
Very beautiful.
Be careful, a step here.
(Holding hands)
What is this?
Did you buy this?
Take a look.
(Gift from Xu Lvyang)
(Congratulations on your new business.
Wishing you success. Liu)
Thank you.
Do you like it?
I like it.
It's beautiful.
It suits this very well.
Yeah, I chose it specially.
There's another gift.
Will you open it?
This is a large lacquer tray.
And this is...
You mentioned to me before
that you really like ancient towns,
gardens, and things like that.
This is a piece by Shen Shao'an.
The name of this lacquer tray
is Wish-Fulfilling Ru Garden.
Ru Garden embodies an Eastern garden.
That's Ru Garden.
Wish-Fulfilling,
wishing your wishes come true.
This shop can be renamed then.
What will it be called?
About this shop's name,
honestly, I hadn't thought
of a good one for it.
Just call it Ru Garden.
Not bad, really.
It actually suits the name quite well.
Do you like it?
I like it.
Distinguished leaders,
dear guests,
let's use the warmest applause
to welcome
our young and handsome Mr. Zhou
to the stage to give a speech.
Distinguished guests,
dear friends,
hello.
Three, two, one.
Grand opening!
It feels like a wedding.
Alright.
Next, we're off to the next venue.
Yes.
I can't help but want to laugh.
Hello.
Really beautiful.
(Jiujiu, Xu Lvyang's friend)
This is my friend, Kitty.
This is my friend, Jiujiu.
Hello.
You are...
Let me introduce you.
This is...
Youling.
This is Youling.
Yeah, my friend from the house.
Yeah.
Okay.
(Through meeting the parents,)
I can't say I understand him completely,
but I definitely
have a better understanding
of another side of him which is
very different from how he was in the house.
I would feel
I really like
these different sides of him.
He also
said to me directly
that he wanted to meet my friends.
He wanted to get to know me better
through my friends.
So I told him
I'd invite him
to have a meal with my friends.
We can calm down
and have a good chat.
(It's a very good process
of getting to know each other.)
Are you feeling cold?
Drape this over you.
(Can't hold it in anymore)
What are you laughing at?
Don't be like that.
We haven't seen each other for too long.
We're very close.
(Can't be serious in front of familiar friends)
We're really close.
We're too close.
Cheers.
Thank you for your hard work.
Happy.
You need to properly assess him.
After all, it's the first time meeting.
Okay.
Properly assess you.
Just putting some pressure on you.
No pressure.
(Not taking the pressure)
So, are you two now
basically
locked in, or
is he still relentlessly courting
our Liu
with his advances?
About this question,
actually, you have to ask Liu.
Because I've been courting her
all along.
Well, have you two
gone anywhere to have fun?
We went to Sanya.
We were there for seven days.
In Sanya,
with such romantic scenery,
did any turning point happen?
Way to bring up the most awkward topic.
It was full of twists and turns.
A lot of stories happened.
Back and forth.
But after coming back from Sanya,
we kind of hung out more.
Yeah, after coming back from Sanya,
we went to an ancient town.
We've been dating continuously.
It was only later
that you spent more time together?
Yeah.
But honestly,
I think in Sanya,
I did something not very suitable.
At that time, I was
very conflicted.
I feel like in Sanya,
I wasn't that happy,
and I made him sad.
Well, we
both...
I was kind of afraid to seek him out.
At that time, we
didn't really talk much
when we saw each other.
I felt
I didn't want to continue
like that with him, so awkwardly,
or rather, so uncomfortably.
So I took the initiative
to seek him out.
I thought I'd take the initiative
to talk to him.
What if she hadn't taken
the initiative to find you?
What would you do?
There's a backstory.
I had sought her out three times
in Sanya.
I think Liu definitely
had some of her own concerns deep down.
Right?
In life, she is a person who
is quite conflicted like this.
She doesn't read people well.
Sometimes, she might
do some things,
and she might not even
realize it herself.
It's after she realizes it later
that she might
do something else.
She will think it through first,
figure it out first,
sort herself out first.
She won't execute it immediately.
Okay.
If she rashly
makes a choice,
actually, for herself,
she might feel
it's not very responsible.
You understand me so well.
If she makes a choice,
she will be very firm.
In love.
About Liu's previous
hesitations
or some
decisions in her choices,
I feel like through learning
from her friends,
I understand she might have some
habits of her own.
Or maybe
she just has this kind of personality.
It might not necessarily be
the kind of thing I imagined,
like deliberate
or
ambiguous relationship.
So I think
for our relationship, it might be
a further step forward.
So, the first thing after recording,
what do you two want to do?
I discovered he actually hasn't been
to the Chulalongkorn area.
I've been to Thailand so many times,
yet I haven't been there.
Yeah, it's amazing.
Saved it to go with her.
Really seems like it.
Really.
Take him on the path of your growth.
Moreover,
the London Eye in the UK,
though I stayed there
for over three years,
I've never ridden it.
You just have to ride it
with the person you love.
Yeah.
I think riding it alone
or riding it with my friends
is meaningless.
So I've never ridden it.
I can already picture it.
Their hands just can't seem
to separate anymore.
I don't know. They're stuck together.
This is the first time your hand
is warmer than mine.
I'm covered by more stuff.
You're cold, right?
I'm okay.
I'll go pay the bill.
Then we'll take a group photo.
Okay, we'll go.
I'll go first.
She is going by herself?
Is it okay for her to go by herself?
I already paid it.
This is done quite well.
It's okay.
I approve of this.
Approved.
I saw her come out, surprised.
Saw her come out, surprised.
What's wrong?
The gentleman on the left
has already paid the bill.
Who paid? It's so hard to guess.
Who paid?
The gentleman on the left paid.
Very considerate.
Thank you.
When did you pay the bill?
Didn't I go to the restroom
after ordering?
(An hour ago)
Is there a place to wash hands?
(Bonus point.)
(A huge bonus point.)
(Yeah, a huge bonus point.)
Hello, boss.
Please help me settle the bill first.
(Zhou Youling secretly pays the bill)
Be faster, please.
Just take my phone here.
So thoughtful.
Not bad.
I believe
in Liu's taste.
Let's go.
See you next time.
Okay.
Hello.
(Xiao Wentao, Jia Peixuan, live music restaurant)
♪Riding on my beloved little motorcycle♪
Peppa Xiao.
He's waiting to be dominated now.
(I really like Wentao like this.)
Let me perform a Chinese song first.
Go ahead.
(Today, I just wanted to formally)
(ask Xuan out)
(and play a trumpet piece
in front of her.)
(I chose a song by Chen Li.)
Because I know
this song is probably something
she would like.
So I chose this song.
I also like Chen Li.
I really like Chen Li.
(Then I thought,)
(since I only know this song,)
(I will figure out this song's)
(melody.)
(I figured it out at the last minute.)
Figuring out the song she likes, right?
(He's about to exude his charm.)
Help.
(Help.)
(I'm done for.)
(Done for.)
(Oh, no.)
(Enchanted.)
(At that moment, suddenly, I)
(felt a sting in my nose,)
(and then my eyes...)
(I forcibly held it back.)
(I thought, no,)
(I absolutely cannot cry
at that moment.)
If you want to cry, just cry.
(I could clearly feel)
(that he was preparing a song.)
(And this song)
(was because he heard me
sing it before.)
(I talked to him about liking Chen Li.)
(I'm very touched.)
(He was seriously preparing this.)
(This couple is really good.)
(I don't even know what to say.)
Hello.
Bear with it,
it might be a little painful.
Why do I choose you every time?
Because for me,
you're always my first choice.
(Want to flaunt with sound and color)
(I want you)
♪With one look from you,
I want to time travel forward♪
Help.
You know the background
behind you is bubbling.
(When he took out the trumpet,)
(I was already...)
(I felt like, "Oh no, he is...")
(I knew what he was going to do.)
(You know?)
(Later, I really couldn't
hold it in anymore.)
(I was watching like this.)
(I could no longer hide that admiration)
(and the look of liking him.)
♪You are the brightest chorus
in my side account♪
Already had those heart-shaped eyes.
How can they be so well-suited?
They are so well-suited
that I'm a bit moved.
Handsome.
♪The salty sea breeze chases
and spirals through your long hair♪
That's so easy.
(I had felt before)
(that he was keeping
his distance from me.)
(Today, it's very obvious
from all the body language.)
(The vehicle is not in motion)
My feet are killing me.
(Even to the point)
(where he took the initiative
to get close to me.)
(Actually, I started feeling it
a bit from last night.)
Lying on her feet.
(He would lie on me and laugh.)
(He would laugh and lean over on me.)
(Normally speaking,)
(it seems like
he's never done this before,)
(leaning on me,
resting on me like that.)
♪They say time is like a ladder,
each step should be taken steadily♪
(Slowly getting closer.)
(Slowly falling for you.)
Give you a massage.
If you want to hold hands,
just hold them.
Yeah.
Don't play this game.
This kind of preamble is all about
wanting to hold hands,
but not having any proper reason
to do so.
So he just plays with the hand first.
He's about to give me a massage.
So comfortable.
I think massaging hands like this
is so comfortable.
(Wentao is indeed
the slow-to-warm-up type.)
(Yes.)
♪Those rounds of bickering and sparring♪
You're so fair.
Stop mocking me.
Why are you so fair?
With our current state,
actually, getting along
is very pleasant,
very relaxed.
I just feel
that there's no need
to worry about the future.
Being happy now is enough.
(Really.)
(Just being happy now is enough.)
Why does the trumpet sound so good?
I like it so much.
Satisfied.
This thing called fate
is really wonderful.
I think they also have a redemption arc.
That's right.
Yeah.
Also a redemption arc.
How can they be so well-suited?
When they piece together,
it's very complete.
Yeah.
Dong.
The delivery is here.
Yeah.
Xuan wants to make some food.
So I...
I ordered some vegetables and stuff.
Why don't we clean this up
together first?
Yeah.
Let's clean up first.
I can't make it now.
I'm about to faint from hunger.
Let me grab a bite first.
You didn't eat outside?
No.
Xuan wants to make
Fish Filets in Hot Chili Oil.
That's how it is when you like someone.
Her name is always on your lips.
What Xuan is going to do.
Where did you go today?
We went to a live music restaurant.
The Shunde dry-steamed dumplings
I ordered are here.
Was it fun today?
Yes, it was fun.
What did you do?
Today, I watched
a wonderful performance.
A wonderful performance.
I saw a very handsome guy.
So incredibly handsome.
(The handsome guy
is holding back a smile)
This one?
Is it this handsome guy?
That goes without saying.
(The handsome guy
is holding back a smile)
Oh, no.
I think this is a little spicy.
What if you can't eat it?
What is a little spicy?
Sauerkraut Fish.
Did you add chili in it?
Try a bite.
Is it spicy?
It's okay.
It's acceptable.
Everything Wentao tastes is sweet.
How could it be spicy?
Mr. Dong.
You are really...
Mr. Dong understands really well.
Hello.
Good evening.
Everyone is back home one after another.
Today, there's...
This plating has something special.
(Text message)
Important notice.
(From today onwards)
From now on,
everyone's semi-mature journey
will enter a 48-hour countdown.
The final 48 hours.
Please cherish the last moments
in the house.
Express things bravely,
face things bravely,
pursue things bravely,
and leave no regrets.
I just feel like
we've spent
almost a month together.
Time goes by fast,
but also very slowly.
It's very slow and very fast.
Actually, a month is not short
to confirm a relationship.
Yeah, it's about right.
Mainly, it's been
an emotionally intense month for them.
Yeah.
I feel like Sanya
was just a few days ago.
I feel like these past few days
back in Shanghai passed in a blur.
It's really so fast.
(I'm starting to feel
the withdrawal effect.)
(It's a faint feeling,)
(like someone is gently tugging at you.)
It's not very painful,
but someone is just
tugging at you from time to time.
I keep thinking
that after it's over,
I'll probably need some time
to get used to it.
(Exclusive note: At the last night
of our time at the house)
(To a certain someone)
Definitely.
(You must have a lot to say)
The emotional intensity is high.
(Please write down)
(The truest thoughts in your heart)
(24 hours left until leaving the house)
It's happening.
Our last meal is very sumptuous.
(Last group dinner)
The dishes are very similar to the first day.
The last supper before the confession.
Ending as a beginning.
Good symbolism.
But on the first day,
I barely ate anything.
Me neither.
On the first day,
we didn't even finish one plate.
But today, I'm thinking,
is this enough for us?
Everyone is no longer holding in.
No one is stiff anymore.
Come on, in pairs,
hurry up and take your seats.
Take your seats in pairs.
(First night)
Let's sit down first.
So sumptuous.
There are happy little sweet drinks.
Let's eat.
What do you want?
Just give me your bowl.
I'll serve you.
Thanks.
I'll just eat on the go.
Just treat it like a buffet.
Is that char siu over there?
Give me some.
I want two pieces of char siu.
What do you want?
I'll get it.
Help me grab some char siu.
Char siu, here you go.
Give me your chopsticks.
This one, right?
Yes.
We're eating much more casually
than the first day.
On the first day, sitting there,
my eyes were constantly moving.
Did you only eat
what was in front of you?
Right, I just kept eating
chicken wings.
I ate six or seven of them.
When I was grabbing the cards just now,
I was thinking,
tomorrow is actually the last day.
Are you happy?
Finally, I can get away from you all.
I really can't stand it.
Master of sarcasm.
I wrote an exclusive note for everyone.
I took one character
from everyone's names,
and incorporated them
into this poem of mine.
The talented scholar is at it again.
This opening is a bit too...
Too much pressure.
You set the bar too high.
You should be the finale.
You go last, bro.
Just go last.
You can't be the first.
Wait, put it down first.
(Forcibly muted)
You're the finale.
Danqi, tell us about yours.
(The new lucky one)
What's going on with you?
Well, mine is very simple.
I wrote this in a flash.
Xuan, I'm going to read it aloud to you.
To Xuan.
Don't be like that.
We promised to keep
our makeup looking nice today.
She's going to make us cry.
It's okay.
From the moment we first met,
I've liked and admired you so much.
The days of playing, eating,
and goofing around together,
the comfort and warmth
of sharing a room with you,
the peace and warmth,
and the many similarities we shared
without even planning them.
You kept me company
while I searched for inspiration.
We cried and laughed together
on rainy nights.
These memories
are precious and irreplaceable.
We both allowed each other
to be ourselves,
seeking joy, chasing freedom,
like the wind.
May we both live life
to the fullest in the real world.
I think moments like this
are very precious for them.
(When I received the letter
Danqi wrote to me,)
(actually, I was quite touched.)
(The memories between us,)
(our respective feelings,)
(It's really a mix of emotions.)
I won't say more.
Okay?
I'll tell you in private later.
Don't cry.
I said mine was very simple,
but after reading it,
I ended up like this.
For the next,
Xuan can go.
I like that.
Okay, sure.
Won't you let me calm down a bit?
Strike while the iron is hot, Xuan.
Strike while the iron is hot.
I wrote this for Xiao Wentao.
Listening.
Maybe my words
fail to express my meaning,
but I'm so happy to have met you.
Because when I'm with you,
I'm always laughing,
and I often feel warm because of you.
Independent kids are used
to holding their own umbrellas,
but you can see the hedgehog inside me,
understand my silence,
and want to hold an umbrella for me.
Spending time with you
made me feel relaxed and at ease.
We play, we mess around, and we chat,
without forcing anything
or having to cater or push.
I almost naturally,
revealed myself little by little.
This is me.
This is the path I've walked,
and these are my experiences.
There's a line in The Little Prince.
If you want to create bonds
with someone,
you must be willing
to risk shedding tears.
I'm not afraid of tears,
but it has to be worth it.
I don't care where we go.
Let's start from here.
Let's hug.
So tight.
A big hug.
♪Cause it doesn't matter
what's down the road♪
These two are wonderful.
So wonderful.
Me too, I like them too.
I like them.
Is this their first hug on screen?
Have you two hugged in private?
♪As long as I've got you next to me♪
You're always like this.
I need to lighten the mood.
I wrote this for everyone.
Xiao Wentao is a great artist
skilled in literature, martial arts,
singing and many instruments.
May I ask, how many horses is this?
No matter how many horses there are,
it doesn't matter.
You can always gallop forward
on your musical path,
and become more and more amazing.
Okay, thank you.
Ruita,
If in the future I could ever give birth
to a daughter like you,
I would wake up laughing every day.
Mom.
Okay, next is Lizheng.
Sorry,
but there really isn't enough space.
So, see you next time.
Thirty thousand words omitted here.
I also wrote this for everyone.
When the sound of the luggage wheels
echo again at the end of the hallway...
Hello.
(This journey that lasts nearly a month)
(of being together day and night)
(is about to come to an end.)
Hello.
(The meeting of twelve people)
(was warm and precious.)
Hello.
(From being awkward at first)
(to sharing everything with each other...)
It was an especially
unforgettable journey.
I'm grateful for this fate.
Here, I not only found love,
but also made
many sincere and lovely
friends from all over the country.
I originally thought
I was more of a cool color,
but all your colors
have made me colorful.
It was your gentleness
that allowed me
to slowly let my guard down
and feel a long-lost sense of peace
in this unfamiliar house.
Is this okay?
(The lively atmosphere
of eating together.)
Chef.
Thank you, Chef.
Thank you, everyone.
Cheers.
(The relaxed moments of chatting
and goofing around together)
(are all especially precious scenes
in my heart.)
Utter chaos.
Right.
So impressive.
♪After a long time,
I'm finally willing to look up♪
♪You're on the other side,
waiting for me to be brave♪
It's out.
Happy birthday.
Don't look at me.
I'll think you're complimenting me.
Why did you assume it was about you?
(The fact that they live together)
(creates intense emotions.)
(It's so much like
a graduation ceremony.)
(Right.)
We can carry her to the balcony first.
One, two, three, up.
This treatment...
That's good.
(Filmed by Chen Danqi)
Looking at this video years later,
we will find
that it will still be touching.
I'm about to cry.
Really.
(Filmed by Ji Yu)
So wonderful.
Record a video.
(Filmed by Chen Danqi)
There are people eating over there,
and here, people are listening to music.
(Filmed by Wang Yi)
May we each go our own way.
May every year be peaceful and safe.
The road ahead is long,
but may flowers accompany us.
Brilliant literary talent.
Ling.
I think you wrote it very well.
Yes.
Come on, Mr. Dong.
A richly colored ending.
A richly colored finale.
Here it comes.
The first line is 'Fill the cup with aged wine,'
(Fill the cup with aged[Chen] wine)
There's the character "Chen".
It's for Chen Jianying.
The second line.
A toast to all friends around.
Youling.
(A toast to all friends around[Zhou])
Come on.
Okay.
The third line.
When we first met in this season,
(When we first met in this season[Ji])
Ji Yu.
It feels like many autumns have passed.
Spring breeze can't untangle emotions,
and daylilies[Xuan]
can't relieve worries,
(This is a bit touching.)
(All of a sudden.)
How rare in life is this?
(How rare[Qi] in life is this)
Danqi.
Let's drink a big cup.
Come on.
How rare in life is this?
Feelings[Yi] should be long sought.
Ruita.
Thank you, Mr. Dong.
Words can't express everything.
I only break a willow branch for you.
(I only break a willow[Liu] branch for you)
When it's time to part, we break a willow branch.
This is a bit impressive.
We'll drink again.
And toast to your
lofty[Ling] aspirations.
Lizheng.
(And toast to your
lofty[Ling] aspirations)
Please keep this memory[Xihui].
Though the road[Lu] is long,
may people endure.
Bingkun.
Thank you.
That's it.
(The poem Dong Zhuoran
wrote for everyone)
That was amazing.
(This is so cool.)
(So cool.)
I'm touched.
But he didn't include himself, right?
It seems not.
Then I'll give my gifts
to everyone.
(Gift-giving segment)
(Right.)
They are my own calligraphy works.
For the girls, it's folding fans,
and for the boys, bookmarks.
When cultured people get sentimental,
it's absolutely breathtaking.
This is for Liu.
You look so beautiful.
For the handsome guy.
And yours.
The only one with no card.
Thank you.
No card, okay.
That's it.
Thank you.
What about Xuan's?
Can I let you all see Xuan's?
Are you kidding?
A special gift.
This is for Xiaowen and Xuan.
This is a plate made in Hungary.
For Xuan,
I picked this out at first sight,
a comb.
It's so pretty.
This is for Danqi and Dong.
Thank you.
So cute.
So beautiful.
I love it.
And this is for BK
and Ruita.
Thank you.
For BK, this is actually
English bear-shaped cookies,
and a piece of British-made wool soap.
Thank you.
For Ruita,
this is a hair tie,
and a canvas bag that I really love.
This is so cute.
And this is
for Hui.
Hui, look at it secretly
when you go back.
Look secretly.
And this is for Lizheng.
Thank you.
For Lizheng, this is a set
of vintage cutlery,
and a caramel sea salt chocolate.
Thank you, thank you, Liu.
And this is for Youling.
A portable sachet.
Because I really like the scent of fig
and fresh grass,
I hope when he wears this sachet,
he can...
Have the scent you like every day.
It can remind him of me.
And finally, this is
a blue thread,
to tie you down.
Tie you down.
Lock it, tie you down.
Brilliant.
A cup.
A lifetime.
Tied together.
I have a plan.
At the entrance of my
newly opened townhouse,
I'll hang a semi-mature sign.
I've drawn
"Unlimited Stay Card" for everyone.
The love of a bossy CEO
is just this practical.
And on the back of Liu's Stay Card,
(To: Xu Lvyang)
maybe I also added an Unlimited Food Card.
(Unlimited Stay Card, Unlimited Eat Card,
Semi-Mature Exclusive)
(Zhou Youling)
Among the myriad
twinkling lights of the city,
Youling has always
kept a light on for us.
Right.
I just hope that in the future,
when you're in Shanghai,
it can be like another home for you.
And if you have a chance,
you can come by and hang out more often.
Thank you, Big Bro.
I didn't write about everyone just now
because what I have for everyone
is all here.
This one is for Dong first.
Thank you.
Because Dong's handwriting is so good,
I didn't dare
to write anything.
So cool.
Thank you.
A drawing.
So nice.
This is for Liu.
This is for you.
I want to give you
the most beautiful crystal ball
in the world.
Thank you.
This is for Xuan.
Such an amazing drawing.
On Xuan's, I printed a lipstick kiss.
Because I often,
when no one is looking,
secretly give Xuan a kiss.
Xiaowen.
This is for you.
Thank you.
Because I remember that day...
(After going through so many things,)
(we've all developed)
(an unspoken understanding.)
(I'm also not very good at using)
(direct language to express)
(my feelings.)
(So I wanted to express them
(through my paintings.)
She incorporated my profession
into my portrait.
You can try to look
at the back of it.
(Be good with Tata)
Okay, got it.
Be good with Ruita.
Got it.
I will.
Thank you.
Where's mine?
Didn't I give you yours before?
In full color.
"Where's mine"?
How should I put it?
Let's just leave that period there.
Come on, cheers.
Everything is in the water.
In the water.
Words are unnecessary.
It's all in the water.
Cheers.
A message came in.
(Text message)
(As life in the house is about to end)
A message came in.
(Please post your last Moments)
It says to post your last Moments
and tell them what you want to say most.
(After sending)
(Please make all your Moments)
Visible to everyone.
(Visible to all)
Everyone can see it.
Visible to all.
But I thought we were only
able to see one person's.
No.
You have to make the previous
previous Moments
all public.
Is that what it means?
Yes.
Because before, you had to set them
to only visible to yourself.
Oh, to make
all the previous ones public.
So all the posts
from day one until today,
will be open to everyone.
That's pretty awkward.
This is pretty awkward.
There's so much stuff, though.
Sometimes, people,
when looking at my past Moments,
really want to set them
to "only visible to me".
We're going to look
at all the Moments later.
Is it making all the Moments
visible to everyone,
or just that one post?
Yes, all Moments visible to everyone.
No way.
Scared, huh?
Why would I be scared?
I'm not scared.
Let's see.
This is so embarrassing.
Because I've written
some long essays before,
the really long kind.
Even though they were meant for myself,
I just feel,
okay,
for that kind of essays to be
seen by everyone,
I feel especially embarrassed.
When I knew my Moments
would be publicly executed,
I was very...
I was a bit nervous.
But it's okay, I guess.
My affections have always been clear,
firm, and brave,
so I don't really have anything
to worry or be afraid of.
Right.
His Moments are basically
written on his face.
Yes.
(Anyway, today is the last day,)
(I'm being honest with myself.)
(I truly wanted to say those words.)
(I feel that after I)
(finish saying this,)
(I won't have any regrets
in the future.)
Everyone, please get ready
to check the Moments.
It's just exposing everything.
Taking the initiative to whom?
Can we even ask that?
(In front of everyone.)
(This is too cruel.)
You have to savor it.
Who are all these?
It's like a QQ Zone.
This is killing me.
(Xu Lvyang)
Thank you.
Locking eyes with me,
who was too shy to look at you.
You have to ponder it, you know?
You have to ponder it.
(The two of us seem
to have a slight misalignment.)
(He might still want
to think about it more.)
Don't do this, okay?
It can't be a plot twist
at this moment, right?
Don't forget.
We have this left.
Alright.
The suspense at the very end
just now.
what will it mean
for their ultimate choice?
I'm curious.
Like,
after everyone sees the past Moments,
for example,
I understand your feelings
at that time,
and your emotions.
If I find out
that your feelings at that time
were different from what I saw,
will it affect my judgment now?
It can't be ruled out
as a hidden danger, right?
Yes, a possibility.
But I think,
it depends on how you interpret it.
If you are looking for evidence
to support your own happiness,
you will think,
"He used to love her so much",
"but he loves me even more."
But if you are looking for evidence
to support your own unhappiness,
you will feel like,
"He seems to love her more than me."
It's really just about how you
choose to interpret it
and how you choose to find evidence.
Most people would still
look for evidence of unhappiness.
Right.
So you have to learn
and train yourself
to look for evidence of happiness,
not the other way around.
This is also a small test.
To see if you can withstand this test.
The confession countdown in the house
has only the final
twenty-four hours left.
Just now, at the end, we saw
everyone's Moments
were about to be made public to all.
So the little thoughts
hidden in the posts
will be seen by everyone.
Everyone will face
their own
final choice.
That is, in the next episode,
(The Final Confession Moment)
there is our ultimate confession.
Everything
will face its final answer.
Restores hair shaft protein
from the root.
Lasting resilience and shine
for three days.
This show is sponsored
by Pantene Pro-V Foam Shampoo.
See you at the finale.
Goodbye.
(Preview)
Everyone, please head to the restaurant together
to check the Moments.
Bingkun and Ruita
already have matching
couple profile pics, look.
I'm about to become a steamer.
A full grid of nine photos posted.
So romantic.
It's really romantic.
I'm actually the awkward one.
See, trouble came from it, right?
I told you not to look.
But you insisted on looking,
and now there's trouble, right?
(The place of origin is opening again)
The beginning of the semi-mature journey
originated from the pull
of a destined tag.
(This segment is carefree.)
(Steady.)
(Prince and princess.)
(This moment is really...)
(This moment is so wonderful.)
True love won't be defeated by reality.
My heart still fluttered helplessly.
This is a very beautiful thing.
This is so romantic.
(To meet the person from the notebook.)
(A fierce confession.)
Here it comes, right?
(Confession moment)